Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Records WAG.022
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: President's Files
  - Subseries II:A: UFT Presidential Files of Charles Cogen.
    - Collective Bargaining, Nov 1961 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Collective Bargaining, Dec 1961 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Collective Bargaining, Jan 1962 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Collective Bargaining, Feb 1962 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Collective Bargaining, Mar 1962 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Collective Bargaining, Apr 1962 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Collective Bargaining, May 1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining, Jun 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Collective Bargaining, Jul 1962 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Collective Bargaining, Aug 1962 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Collective Bargaining, Sep 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Collective Bargaining, Oct 1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Collective Bargaining, Nov 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Collective Bargaining, Dec 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Collective Bargaining, Jan 1962 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Collective Bargaining, Feb 1962 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Collective Bargaining, Mar 1962 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Collective Bargaining, Apr 1962 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Collective Bargaining, May 1963-Jun 1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Collective Bargaining, Jul 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Collective Bargaining, Aug 1963 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Collective Bargaining, Sep 1963 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining, Oct 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining: Agreement, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Collective Bargaining: Aid from Other Unions, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings, Apr 1960-Jun 1961 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings, Jul 1961-Nov 1961 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings, Dec 1961-Mar 1962 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings (I), Apr 1962 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings (II), Apr 1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings (III), Apr 1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Collective Bargaining: Clippings, May 1962-Nov 1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Collective Bargaining: Committee to Achieve Collective Bargaining Status, Clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Collective Bargaining: Informational Material, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Committee Chairmen, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Communism, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Community Education, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Community Schools: Compulsory Education Law, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Conditions in Schools: Class Size and Fire Hazards, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Conditions in Schools: Staffing Difficult Schools, 1961, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Conflict with National Education Association (NEA), 1961-1964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Conflict with Teachers' Union, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Constitution, 1960, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Constitution Revision Committee: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Constitution Revision Committee: Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Constitution Revision Committee: Revised Constitution, Amendments, and By-Laws, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Contract, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Contracts: Stevenson School, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Decentralization, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Delegate Assembly: Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Delinquency, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Dieticians Chapter, 1960-1962, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Discounts, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Dissidents: Blumin, Arthur, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Dissidents: JHS 101X, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Dissidents: Kamachi, David, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Dissidents: Koppersmith, Hal, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Dissidents: Miscellaneous, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Dissidents: Rights of UFT Members, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - District Publications, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Education Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Educational Journal Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Educational Journal Committee: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Elections, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Elections, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Elementary Affairs Committee: Minutes, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Elementary School Committee, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Elementary Schools, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Elementary Schools: Newsletters, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Elementary School Teachers Association, Inc., 1961, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Eligible Lists, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Empire State Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Evening High School Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Examination Procedures, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Examinations: NTE and other Methods of Certification, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Excessing, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Extra Curricular Activities Committee, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Finances: Accounting, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Finances: Bonds and Loans, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Finances: Budget, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Finances: Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Finances: Dues, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Goldberg, Arthur: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Goldman, Louis: Testimonial, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Grievance Committee, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Griggs, Allen: "An Evaluative Study of the Aims, Structure and History of the UFT", 1961 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Health Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Health and Safety Committee, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Higher Horizons Program, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - High School Teachers Association and High Schools, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - History (UFT), 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Homebound Chapter, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Human Relations Committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Human Relations Committee, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Human Rights, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Industrial Arts Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Integration, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Joint Committee of Teachers Organizations, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Junior High Schools, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 139 Bronx, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Kolodny, Jules: Correspondence, 1964-1966, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Kolodny, Jules: Speeches/Statements, 1962, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Kolodny, Jules: Writings, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Laboratory Assistants Chapter, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Laboratory Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Leave of Absence: Sick Leave, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Legal, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Legislative Committee, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Lefkowitz Scholarship Awards, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Library Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Mailing / Announcements (including Bargaining), 1960-1961, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Mayor's Mediation Panel, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Meetings and Workshops: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Militancy, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Music Teachers Committee, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - National Education Association (NEA): City Teachers Association, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - NEA: New York City Educator, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - News Releases: UFT, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - News Releases: UFT, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - New York City Board of Education: Board of Ed. vs. Jim Council, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - New York University Federation of United Professionals: Newsletter, undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Non-Classroom Personnel, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Non-NYC Public Schools: Newsletters, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Non-Public Schools, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Office Employees International Union, Local 153, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Office Management, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Opposition: STAFF Newsletter, Jan 1966 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Oral History Interview with Charles Cogen, Jul 25, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Organizing, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Organizing, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Organizing, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Organizing: Expenses, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Pacheco, Joseph, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Paraprofessionals, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Parent-Teachers Association, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Parrish, Richard: AFT Vice President, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Pension, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Pension, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Pension, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Pension, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Personnel: Fire, Hire and Pay, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Political Action, undated, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 3a)
    - Press Releases, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Prince Edward County, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Public Relations, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations: Voice of the Teacher Radio Program, 1961, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations: WINS Pilot Study, "Problems and Dangers in the NYC Public Schools", 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Public Schools and Students, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Queens Teachers Association, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Reading Improvement Teachers, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Relations with Other Unions, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Relations with Other Unions: Support from Other Unions, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Reorganization of Schools, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Sabbatical Leave: Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Salary: Comparisons with other Schools, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Salary Committee, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Salary Committee, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Salary Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Salary Committee: Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Salary Credit: Bonus for Special Service Schools, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Salary Credit: Differentials/Promotional Increments, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Salary Credit: Single Salary, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Salary Credit: Workers Progress Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - School Finance: Federal Aid to Education, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - School Finance: New York City, 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - School Finance: New York State, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - School Safety: Overcrowding, 1944, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 25E)
    - School Secretaries Chapter, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - School Secretaries Chapter: Newsletter, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Secondary Schools Teachers Association, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Selden, David: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Selden, David: Presentations and Speeches, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Selden, David: Published Articles, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Simonson, Rebecca, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Social Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Socialism: New Party, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Special Committee of 600 Schools, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Special Service Schools, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Spring Conference, undated, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Spring Conference, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Spring Conference, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Spring Conference, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Staffing Difficult Schools, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Staffing Difficult Schools, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Staff Relations Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Staff Rotation Plan, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - State-Wide Committee for School Support, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Strike Committee: Informational Material, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Strike Committee: Right to Strike, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Strike Committee: Right to Strike, Clips, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Strikes, 1952, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Strikes, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1a)
    - Strikes, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Strikes, 1964-1969 (Box 22, Folder 2a)
    - Substitutes Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Summer School: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 3a)
    - Supervisors Pay Index, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Taxation, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 4a)
    - Teacher Recruitment Drive, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Teacher Rights, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Teacher Rights: Health Exams, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Teacher Rights: Legislation, 1960, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Teachers Bargaining Organization of New York, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Teacher Training, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Teachers' Union, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Teachers' Union: Teachers' Union/Teachers Guild Split, UFT Related, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Teachers' Union: Teachers Unity, UFT, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Tenure, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Terminal Leave, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Travel Committee, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Travel Committee: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Union Education Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - United Action, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - United Federation of College Teachers, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - United Federation of College Teachers, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - United Federation of College Teachers, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - United Federation of College Teachers: Community College UFT Reporter, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - United Teacher, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Urban Development, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Veterans, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Vocational Schools, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Vocational Schools: Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Volunteers, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Welfare Fund, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Welfare Fund, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Welfare Fund: Survey of Welfare Fund Plans in other Cities, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Working Conditions, 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Working Conditions: Lunch Periods, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Working Conditions: Non-Teaching, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Working Conditions: Overcrowding, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Work Stoppage, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Work Stoppage, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Work Stoppage: Informational Material, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Subseries II:B: UFT Presidential Files of Albert Shanker, 1935-1996.
    - Academic Freedom, 1965-1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom: Kraus Case, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Academic Freedom: Rafferty, Max, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Academic Freedom: Selzer, Prof. Michael (Brooklyn College), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Accounting, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save Our Schools, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save Our Schools, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save Our Schools, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save Our Schools, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save Our Schools, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Adult Education, 1964-1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Affirmative Action, 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Affirmative Action: Bakke Case, 1974-1978 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - AFL-CIO, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - AFL-CIO, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - AFL-CIO: American Federationist, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - AFL-CIO: American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - AFL-CIO: Civil Rights Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - AFL-CIO: Communications Workers of America, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - AFL-CIO: Department for Professional Employees, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - AFL-CIO: Department for Professional Employees, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - AFL-CIO: Department for Professional Employees, 1977-1983 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - AFL-CIO: Department for Public Employees, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - AFL-CIO: Internal Disputes Plan, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD (Industrial Union Department), 1962-1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD (Industrial Union Department) Newsletters, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - AFL-CIO: Labor Education, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - AFL-CIO: Labor, Money and Politics: A Reference Manual for Union Political Directors, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO: New York State, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO: Pension Plan Report, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - AFL-CIO: Reagan Economic Policies, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO: Trade and Industrial Department Reports, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - African-American Labor Center, 1966-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - African-American Teachers Association (formerly Negro Teachers Association), 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - African-American Teachers Association (formerly Negro Teachers Association), 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - African-American Teachers Association, Black News, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - African-American Teachers Association, Forum, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - African-American Teachers Association, Forum, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - African-Americans, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - AFSCME, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - AFSCME: DC37, 1963-1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - AFSCME: DC37, 1972-1979 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Agency Fee, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Agency Fee, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Agency Fee, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Airline Strike, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Altomare, George, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Amalgamated Bank, 1965-1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1967-1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1967-1977 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - American Assembly, 1966-1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1964-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - American Association of School Administrators, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1974-1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1978-1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American Bar Association, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1961-1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1966-1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1966-1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - American Jewish Congress: Public Statements and Reports, 1966-1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - American School Board Journal, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1966-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Amnesty International, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Amnesty International Education Project, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Amsterdam News, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Another View(UFT Member Newsletter), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Bulletin(ADL newsletter), 1969-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Bulletin(ADL newsletter), 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Correspondence and Memos, 1967-1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Decentralization, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Anti-Defamation League: P.A.R.E. (People against Racism in Education), 1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Press Releases, 1971-1974 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Publications, 1969-1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Anti-Semitism, 1969-1978 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Apartheid, Committee of Conscience against, 1965-1986 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Arbitrations, 1963-1969 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Arbitrations, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Arbitrations, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Arbitrations, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Arbitrations, 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Arbitrations, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Arbitrations: Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) Panel, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Arbitrators, 1966-1982 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Arden House High School Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Ashe, Bernard, 1974-1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Ashmore, Harry, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Asian-American Free Labor Institute, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Aspira, 1966-1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Assistant Teachers, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, 1967-1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Association for Union Democracy, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Association of NYC Educators, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Attendance Teachers Chapter, 1967-1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Attendance Teachers Chapter: NEA Takeover Campaign, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Attendance Teachers Chapter: Truancy Task Force, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Automation House, 1970-1975 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Auxiliary Teachers, 1964-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Bank Street College of Education, 1966-1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Barnard School Chapter, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Development and Services Corp, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Beichman, Arnold, 1970-1977 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Bennett, William (Secretary of Education), 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Better Buying Service, 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Bias Suits: CCNY Center for Biomedical Education, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Bilingual Education, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Bilingual Education, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Bilingual Education, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Bilingual Education, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Bilingual Education, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Bilingual Education, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Biographical Files, 1960-1969 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Biographical Files, 1970-1979 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Biographical Files, 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Biographical Files: National Elementary Principal, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Biographical Files: Run for AFT Presidency, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Biographical Files: UFT Publications, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Black Americans to Support Israel Committee, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Black Trade Unionists Committee, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Blaine Amendment, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Block Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Blum, Eugene, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - B'nai B'rith, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)